const essentialsChapter6QuizData = [
  {
    id: "6_1",
    question: "What is the key to customer satisfaction? (Page 85)",
    options: ["Providing value", "Being their friend", "Doing a job that is just good enough", "Cutting corners to finish jobs quicker than expected"],
    answer: "Providing value"
  },
  {
    id: "6_2",
    question: "Most people have chimneys. Therefore, customers usually understand the intricacies of proper and sound venting principles (Page 85)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "6_3",
    question: "_________ are paramount to delivering exceptional customer service. (Page 85)",
    options: ["Communication skills", "Big words to make you sound smart", "Treating the customer as if they don't know anything", "Tech skills"],
    answer: "Communication skills"
  },
  {
    id: "6_4",
    question: "Since the customer can't see you on the phone, they won't perceive your attitude. (Page 85)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "6_5",
    question: "When you are on your way, or going to be late, it is good practice to _________. (Page 86)",
    options: ["Call the customer", "Think of a good excuse to use if you are going to be late", "Surprise them without letting them know", "Email the customer"],
    answer: "Call the customer"
  },
  {
    id: "6_6",
    question: "If you drive aggressive or reckless while in a company vehicle, that reflects on _________. (Page 86)",
    options: ["The company", "You", "The customer", "The vehicle manufacturer"],
    answer: "The company"
  },
  {
    id: "6_7",
    question: "Once you get to the customer's house, you should wait in your truck for a long time. (Page 86)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "6_8",
    question: "The longer you wait in the vehicle before coming to the door, the more _________ your customer may become. (Page 86)",
    options: ["Happy", "Relaxed", "Agitated", "Hopeful"],
    answer: "Agitated"
  },
  {
    id: "6_9",
    question: "Remove any glasses or non-uniform hats and leave them in the truck before going to the customer. (Page 86)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "6_10",
    question: "Have your _________ or business card ready to present to the customer to assure them you are the person they are expecting. (Page 86-87)",
    options: ["CSIA Photo ID", "Driver's License", "Passport", "Social Security Card"],
    answer: "CSIA Photo ID"
  },
  {
    id: "6_11",
    question: "Once you ring the doorbell, _________. (Page 87)",
    options: ["Step back 2 or 3 feet away from the door", "Yell who you are so they know who is there", "Say 'Housekeeping'", "Begin to open the door and go in"],
    answer: "Step back 2 or 3 feet away from the door"
  },
  {
    id: "6_12",
    question: "When talking to the customer it is fine to display arrogance because you are certified. (Page 87)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "6_13",
    question: "Before entering the house, _________. (Page 87)",
    options: ["Put on boot covers", "Walk directly to the living room", "Take the customer's picture", "Get just inside the house and then clean your shoes off so you don't track stuff any further"],
    answer: "Put on boot covers"
  },
  {
    id: "6_14",
    question: "When entering the home, the most important thing to do is _________. (Page 87)",
    options: ["Ask them what they did wrong", "Listen", "Make sure they know you are certified by the way you talk", "Talk bad about other companies to boost your companies reputation"],
    answer: "Listen"
  },
  {
    id: "6_15",
    question: "You should always ask permission first before using the customer's furniture, tools or bathroom. (Page 87)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "6_16",
    question: "You are an adult. It is alright to swear or use crude language in front of, or directly to a customer in conversation. (Page 87)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "6_17",
    question: "It is always best to accompany your written reports with _________. (Page 87)",
    options: ["Charges", "Photos", "As little info as possible", "Notes about the customer's behavior"],
    answer: "Photos"
  },
  {
    id: "6_18",
    question: "What should you do with the area where you have been working before you leave. (Page 87)",
    options: ["Clean it up entirely", "Leave tools, drop cloths, etc, so that future work is quicker", "Write your company's name", "Pick up the tools and drop cloths only. The customer is responsible for sweeping the dust."],
    answer: "Clean it up entirely"
  },
  {
    id: "6_19",
    question: "Before leaving, make sure the customer has your business card and contact information. Then shake their hand and thank them for their business. (Page 87)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "6_20",
    question: "As you prepare to leave a customer's house, this is the perfect time to _________. (Page 87)",
    options: ["Use their restroom", "Set up an appointment for next year's service", "Confront them if they said anything bad about you", "Try and sneak in a hidden charge on their invoice"],
    answer: "Set up an appointment for next year's service"
  },
];

if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 6: Professional Etiquette'] = essentialsChapter6QuizData;
